Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science East West Institute Of Technology, Bengaluru <u>deepakrama321@gmail.com</u> <u>GitHub</u> LinkedIn

ABOUT

As a committed computer science student, I possess a strong passion for leveraging my technical expertise to tackle intricate challenges and offer inventive solutions. Fueled by a profound affinity for problem-solving and a creative mindset, I am enthusiastic about applying my knowledge and fervor to effect substantial change in the realm of technology.

Education

Year	Degree/Certificate	Institute	CGPA/Percentage
2020-Current	B.E in Computer Science	East West Institute Of Technology	8.4
2019-2020	Burbank Unified School District	Burbank High School	90%
2018	Burbank Unified School District	Burbank High School	92%

Experience

· Accurate Info Solution

Sep 2023 - Nov 2023

Freelance Web developer

Bengaluru

- Created a precision-focused WordPress website for accurate info solution. Implemented custom features to enhance user experience
- link to view: Accurate info solution
- Skills: Skills: Wordpress, Hostinger, WhatsApp Integration, email SMTP integration

- Afforal

Django intern

Jan 2023- Feb 2023

Location

- Developed a robust fitness web application
- Employed SQLite for database management
- Implemented user authentication system for secure access.
- Skills:Django,Python, SQL,HTML,CSS,JS

Projects

• ML Repository

AIML

Github

This is a repository that contains different models of Machine Learning classified accordingly This repository is a comprehensive collection of machine learning models.

- The repository also includes example datasets, Jupyter notebooks for training and evaluating these models.
- Skills: Seaborn, Matplotlib, Scikit-learn, Numpy, Regression models

Diabetes Prediction

Apr 2023

ML

Github

- machine learning model to predict diabetes risk using comprehensive health and demographic data.
- Used powerful tools such as Gradio to deploy the prediction model
- Skills: Python, Pandas, Seaborn, Matplotlib, Scikit-learn, Numpy

WasteBucks
 DBMS
 Github

- A web application which connects the vendors to wholesale dealers in reusable waste.
- Effectively used PHP to connect to SQL Databases while understanding concepts of different Keys and Triggers
- Skills: PHP,HTML,CSS,JS,SQL,Bootstrap

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- · Programming Languages: Python, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, C++
- · Advanced Programming Skills: NodeJS, ExpressJS, Pandas, Numpy, SQL
- Other Skills : Github, Wordpress
- · Operating Systems: Windows, Linux & Android

KEY COURSES TAKEN

- · The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp
- · Learn Python Programming Masterclass
- · Machine Learning A-ZTM: AI, Python

Certifications

- Databases and SQL for Data Science with Python: IBM
- Python Programming Specialization: University of Michigan
- Certificate Name Certifying Institution Name

COMPETITIVE CODING

- Codewars Deepak-vaduganambi
- Leetcode <u>Deepak-vaduganambi</u>

Miscellaneous

• open source contribution, contributed to Hacktoberfest on greedy algorithm 2023

• Pitcher perfect, teams pitched their innovative start-up ideas. My team secured second place

Last updated: December 16, 2023

2022